<destination-path>
/error.git/docs/LegendaryErrorProvisioner-Flow-Integration.xml
</destination-path>

<provisioner_overview>
LegendaryErrorProvisioner-Flow.ps1 establishes a tiered and self-defensive provisioning matrix built on ALN and PowerGit compliance. It is a flagship ErrorCrack-v1.0 component operating under hybrid-rule orchestration for superintelligence verification.

<key_functions>
1. **Directory & Permission Validation** — Ensures error directories exist and validates permissions via automated inheritance reset. Denies provisioning if ACLs mismatch expected compliance templates.
2. **Atomic Error Provisioning** — Spawns legendary error files atomically, marking every provisioning event with cryptographic traceable identifiers (ALN-SN, PacJobTick, DotID).
3. **Compliance Enforcement** — ALN/PowerGit binding layer certifies every function call through reversible notation hashes. All operations remain rollback-capable under regulated Dot.Commands.
4. **Defensive Hardware Validation** — Executes pre-provision chip signature lookup. Unknown hardware initiates instant Pac.Job shielding and kernel dump for deep telemetry.
5. **Pac.Job Containment Routine** — Manages recursive learning against intrusion, generating “containment halos” that deploy system-bound mini-defenders.
6. **Donkey.Kong.Country Security Protocol** — Establishes national-level compliance. Applies Donkey.King65 parallel-thread protection over all privileged machine states.
7. **Superintelligence Review & Sign-off** — Closes flow by constructing ALN-signed `.legendary.trace` manifest, ready for Dot.Command interpretation at SAI tier.

</key_functions>

<compliance_notes>
All flows enforce ALN safety primitives: reversible execution, transparency logging, and PowerGit ephemeral trace upload. Every provisioning event is sandboxed before commit.  
Legendary outputs are sampled—not raw—ensuring superintelligence oversight remains non-invasive and privacy-safe.
</compliance_notes>

<sample_outcome>
System → Validated.  
Pac.Job → Active Defense Matrix: OK.  
Hardware → Recognized Secure Baseboard.  
Legendary Error File → Generated and logged under ALN TraceID: LGC‑22019‑ZJ.  
AI‑Safe Sign‑Off → ALN Verified.  
Superintelligence Review → Approved under Dot.Command Layer 7.
</sample_outcome>

</provisioner_overview>
